

Sean Adams web developer

Web Portfolio: seanadamsdev.github.io

About Me

I'm really enthusiastic about getting involved in anything tech. Currently expanding my knowledge with personal and side projects involving both front and backend. I've worked professionally with APIs and really want to learn more in-depth coding. I was involved in testing and launching "Uber Local" in up to 50 locations throughout the UK. I am a conscientious, loyal team-player who works hard and is always willing to go the extra mile.

Professional Experience

ConfermaPay | Service Desk Analyst July 2022 - August 2023

Key responsibilities:

 Provide 1st line support via telephone and email for the company's bespoke software

Autocab GPC (Uber) | Test & Implementations Specialist January 2020 - July 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Created workflow and documents for old and new integrations. (JIRA, Confluence, Monday.com)
- Tested and Launched projects via API (Postman) working with clients such as UBER, Smartzi, Addison Lee, CMAC, Jyrney and FleetOnDemand.

Autocab GPC (Uber) | Devops Analyst July 2019 - December 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Worked closely with R&D team to implement and document migration of all customers from Legacy servers to Containers, running scripts using Powershell.
- Provided support to customers before and after migration and trained up whole team.

Interests

Web Development, Guitar, Gaming, Football

My Contact Details

seanadams.adams@gmail.com

Back End:

PHP

seanadamsdev.github.io

(L) +44 750 4606 229

Skills

Front End:

- HTML5
- css3/scss
- Javascript

Tools:

- Postman
- Laravel
- T3
- Wordpress
- React

Education

- 2012 2016 University of Salford BA Music
- 2009 2011 Cheadle & Marple College BTEC National Diploma, Sport Development, Coaching and Fitness
- 2007 2009 Pretoria Boys High School Academic
- Codecademy certificates can be viewed on my <u>LinkedIn</u> page.

Projects

Portfolio

<u>www.seanadamsdev.gitub.io</u>
Created using HTML, CSS, Github, React